Mulualm Defersha

| 054-2962914|mulualm1997@gmail.com|

Full Stack software developer (web)...

Experienced in positions that require teamwork, working under pressure with multiple interfaces.

Works well independently and as a part of a team, excellent interpersonal skills, fast learner. Motivated, goal-oriented, meets goals of productivity and schedule.

Education and Courses

2019 - 2020: Tech Career (Technology boot-camp) - A professional course of 800+ hours

Databases >> SQL Server, Mongo dB
Server-side >> C#, Nodejs & Express
Client-side >> Html, Css, JavaScript
Framework >> Bootstrap, React

Joint final project with AT&T - Connection between lecturers and clients.

2015-2019: - Full matriculation, Amit High School. Ashdod.

- * Received certificate of excellence upon graduation.
- * Major subject: Electronics.

Employment experience

2018 - 2020: Security guard at a strategic facility of Noble Energy. the job included:

- Tours, drills, medical staff responsibilities and firefighting.
- Training of new employees, overlap, and training procedures

The position required:

• Professionalism, great responsibility, teamwork, 24/7 work.

Military Service

2015-2018: Platoon sergeant and fighter in the Kefir Brigade. Completed with the rank of First Sergeant.

- Rifleman 08, Fighter, platoon commander, platoon sergeant, RPG liaison.
- Responsibility for the platoon agenda and daily routine, training the fighters in the shooting range, and company communications equipment.
- The job required: leadership, responsibility, working under pressure, adhering to strict schedules, seriousness and teamwork.

Languages

Hebrew: mother tongue English: high level